[{"Question":"Abase","Options":["Humiliate","Anger","Defy","Spend"],"Answer":"Humiliate"},
{"Question":"Abjure","Options":["Sanctify","Pitiful","Renounce","Abolish"],"Answer":"Renounce"},
{"Question":"Atrophy","Options":["Victimize","Decay","Resist","To reward"],"Answer":"Decay"},
{"Question":"Bourgeoies","Options":["French Victory Ritual","King","Peasant","Capitalist"],"Answer":"Capitalist"},
{"Question":"Cacophany","Options":["Opera","Disharmonious Sound","Pleasant sound pleasing the ego","Account Book"],"Answer":"Disharmonious Sound"}
{"Question":"Clandestine","Options":["Luxurious","Secret","Merciful","Priest"],"Answer":"Secret"},
{"Question":"Coagulate","Options":["Clot","Sing Together","Rebel","Thin"],"Answer":"Clot"},
{"Question":"Consecrate","Options":["Destroy","Dedicate","Antagonize","Meditate"],"Answer":"Dedicate"},
{"Question":"Deleterious","Options":["Chaotic","Harmful","Diplomatic","Spendthrift"],"Answer":"Harmful"},
{"Question":"Garrulous","Options":["Wordy","Wild","Stubborn","Dangerous"],"Answer":"Wordy"},
{"Question":"Hegemony","Options":["Plagiarisim","Obdurate","Organizing","Domination"],"Answer":"Domination"},
{"Question":"Ignominious","Options":["Ill omened","Poor","Humiliating","Ignorant"],"Answer":"Humiliating"},
{"Question":"Maudlin","Options":["Weakly Sentimental","Overly Aggressive","Extremely Interesting",""],"Answer":"Fiercely Independent"},
{"Question":"Obstreperous","Options":["Noisy","Stubborn","Resilient","Jealous"],"Answer":"Noisy"},
{"Question":"Perfunctory","Options":["Smell","Persisting","No Enthusiasm","Mundane"],"Answer":"No Enthusiasm"},
{"Question":"Sagacity","Options":["Shrewdness","Stinginess","Ignorance","Fiercely Independent"],"Answer":"Shrewdness"}]